Finding Aid for the George Mitchell Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
George Mitchell Collection
1850-1952
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0294
.21 linear feet
Scope and Content
This .21 linear feet collection contains a stock certificate, three pamphlets, and 18 playbills/program. The collection is arranged by subject, then by date.
- Certificate - Stock
  - Aldelphi Theatre Company, 1850
- Pamphlets
  - Jack Robinson and his Monkey
    - A melodrama in two acts, London Theatres
  - The Tower of London, 1947
  - The English-Speaking World 1951
- Playbills/Programs
  - Concert
    - Union Female College, June 27, 1867
  - Singin Skewl
    - Aleck Couric’s Show House, 1876
  - The King’s Fool and the Gypsy Baron, 1891
  - The Littlest Rebel, 1913
  - America — A Spiritual Adventure
    - Ward-Belmont School of Expression, November 15, 1920
  - Pygmalion
    - Nashville Community Playhouse, 1949
  - Second Pop Concert
    - The Nashville Symphony Orchestra, April 22, 1951
  - Second Pop Concert
    - The Nashville Symphony Orchestra, April 22, 1951
  - South Pacific
    - Majestic Theatre, 1951
  - Concert Bulletin
    - Boston Symphony Orchestra Seventy-first season, 1951-1952
  - Bell, Book, and Candle
    - Ethel Barrymore Theatre, 1951
  - Venus Observed
    - New Century Theatre, 1952
  - Gigi
    - Fulton Theatre, 1952
  - Carmen
    - Metropolitan Opera, 1952
  - I am a Camera
    - Empire Theatre, 1952
  - Don Juan in Hell
    - Plymouth Theatre, 1952
  - Jane
    - Coronet Theatre, 1952
  - Caesar and Cleopatra
    - Nashville Community Playhouse, 1952
  - Olivet to Calvary
    - St. Cecilia Society of Washington Seminary, n.d.